domainhostingpromo.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Domain and Hosting Promo Codes

At **DomainHostingPromo.com** , we are committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to this Website and as our customer. To our visitors and to our customers, we offer this pledge:

We will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transmit, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection**

When you send us email from this Website, you will provide us with certain personally identifiable information including your email address. At anytime, if you wish to no longer receive correspondaces via email, please contact us via the address listed on our site under the “Contact” link.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive while they are visiting this Website. We may utilize a short-lived form of cookie when you visit this site. At **DomainHostingPromo.com** , a cookie is only used to identify one unique visitor from another visitor during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server. We may use cookie technology during a session as a tool to carry forward your input information during the enrollment process. This enables the visitor to input their information once and have the information appear later during the enrollment process. No personally identifiable information is stored on the cookie. The cookie expires and is deleted from the visitor’s computer as soon as they close their browser.

**Third Party Links**

This Website may contain links to third party Websites that are not controlled by **DomainHostingPromo.com**. These third party links are made available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that the **DomainHostingPromo.com** is not responsible for the content of third party Websites linked to the **DomainHostingPromo.com** nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third party Websites linked to the **DomainHostingPromo.com**. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are at and while you are actively in a session with the **DomainHostingPromo.com**. If you should link to a third party Website from the **DomainHostingPromo.com** , we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that Website’s privacy policy.

**Changes In Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make the changes.
